Melville S. Munro Papers MS036
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Tufts College history, 1858 -- 1943; 1920 -- 1936; MS036.008; 1.75 Linear Feet; 58 Digital Object(s)
  - Miscellaneous pictures through the years, 1913 -- 1930; MS036.008.022 (Box 22)
    - A Scene from "Gold In The Hills", MS036.008.022.00798; Munro, Melville S. (Box 22)
      mounted on 8 x 10 in: M. S. Munro, Miscellaneous pictures through the years, Vol. 1, p. 31. The city slicker lures the farmer's daughter.
      Theater; Student activities; photographic print; Pen, Paint, and Pretzels
    - Scene from "Gold In The Hills", MS036.008.022.00799; Munro, Melville S. (Box 22)
      mounted on 8 x 10 in: M. S. Munro, Miscellaneous pictures through the years, Vol. 1, p. 30. Irate father banishes wayward daughter from home.
    - From "Berkely Square" - An Alumni Dramatics Production, MS036.008.022.00800; Munro, Melville S. (Box 22)
      mounted on 8 x 10 in: M. S. Munro, Miscellaneous pictures through the years, Vol. 1, p. 29
      Theater; photographic print
    - Students training for WWI, Fletcher Field, 1913; MS036.008.022.00801; Munro, Melville S. (Box 22)
      mounted on 8 x 10 in: M. S. Munro, Miscellaneous pictures through the years, Vol. 1, p. 28. A Student Company was formed in anticipation of our entering the World War and used the old campus (Fletcher Field) as a training field
      World War, 1914-1918; photographic print
    - Removing bedding from West Hall barracks, 1916; MS036.008.022.00802; Munro, Melville S. (Box 22)
      mounted on 8 x 10 in: M. S. Munro, Miscellaneous pictures through the years, Vol. 1, p. 27. From West Hall Barracks the last load of bedding is trucked away. The student "gobs" serving as "cleaner-uppers;" a picture of World War days on the Hill
    - Lieut. Harmon and Eddie Cook boxing, 1925; MS036.008.022.00803; Munro, Melville S. (Box 22)
      mounted on 8 x 10 in: M. S. Munro, Miscellaneous pictures through the years, Vol. 1, p. 26. Lieut. Harmon - our famous boxing instructor shows "Eddie" Cook how it is done
      Athletics; Boxing; photographic print; Harmon, Lieutenant; Cook, Eddie
    - The girls like basketball, MS036.008.022.00804; Munro, Melville S. (Box 22)
      mounted on 8 x 10 in: M. S. Munro, Miscellaneous pictures through the years, Vol. 1, p. 25
      Athletics; Women; Basketball; photographic print
    - An Anxious Moment in Cousens Gymnasium - Men's Basketball, MS036.008.022.00805; Munro, Melville S. (Box 22)
      mounted on 8 x 10 in: M. S. Munro, Miscellaneous pictures through the years, Vol. 1, p. 24
      Athletics; Basketball; photographic print
    - Some folks like to gettied up into knots and join the wrestling squad, MS036.008.022.00806; Munro, Melville S. (Box 22)
      mounted on 8 x 10 in: M. S. Munro, Miscellaneous pictures through the years, Vol. 1, p. 23
      Athletics; Wrestling; photographic print
    - Fencing is coming into favor as an activity, MS036.008.022.00807; Munro, Melville S. (Box 22)
      Athletics; Fencing; photographic print
    - From "The Queen's Husband" - A 3P's Production, MS036.008.022.00808; Munro, Melville S. (Box 22)
      mounted on 8 x 10 in: M. S. Munro, Miscellaneous pictures through the years, Vol. 1, p. 33
    - When Leo [Lewis] ran dramatics ..., MS036.008.022.00809; Munro, Melville S. (Box 22)
      mounted on 8 x 10 in: M. S. Munro, Miscellaneous pictures through the years, Vol. 1, p. 34
      photographic print; Lewis, Leo R.; Pen, Paint, and Pretzels
  - To the Carmichaels from the Munros at Tufts College..., 1876 -- 1930; MS036.008.023.00001 (Box Shared 136)
    - The Jackson Freshman Button, 1930; MS036.008.023.00001.00384; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 86)
      Munro, Tufts College - A Lecture Part 3 Activities, Volume 4
      People; Students; photographic print; Jackson College
    - Sliding into third base, 1930; MS036.008.023.00001.01399; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 136)
      Melville S. Munro Collection - MS036/008-023#001
    - The College Bookstore (Florence Reed Campman J 1936 and unidentified second person), 1930; MS036.008.023.00001.01400; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 136)
      Melville S. Munro Collection, MS036/008-023#001; female student is Florence Reed Campman, J 1936, as identified by her daughter Barbara McFarlane Wright.
      People; Students; photographic print; Bookstore
    - A demonstration at the medical school, 1930; MS036.008.023.00001.01401; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 136)
      Melville S. Munro Collection, MS036/008-023#001
      Academic; People; Faculty; Students; photographic print; School of Medicine
    - Class of 1876, MS036.008.023.00001.01402; Unknown (Box Shared 136)
      Melville S. Munro Collection, MS036/008-023#002-pg.17
      Students; photographic print
    - The old post office building, 1900; MS036.008.023.00001.01404; Unknown (Box Shared 136)
      Melville S. Munro Collection - MS036/008-023#003-pg.10
      Buildings; photographic print
    - The interior of the old post office building, 1900; MS036.008.023.00001.01405; Unknown (Box Shared 136)
  - Tufts College: a lecture, history, 1875 -- 1943; MS036.008.023.00002 (Box Shared 136)
    - Gardner C. Anthony, MS036.008.023.00002.00373; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 86)
      from Munro, Tufts College - A Lecture Part 1 History, Volume 2, p. 28
      People; Faculty; photographic print; Anthony, Gardner Chace
    - The College Seal, 1943; MS036.008.023.00002.00374; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 86)
      from Munro, Tufts College - A Lecture Part 1 History, Volume 2, p.1
      Seals; photographic print
    - Thomas J. Sawyer, MS036.008.023.00002.00375; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 86)
      from Munro, Tufts College - A Lecture Part 1 History, Volume 2, p. 11
      People; Faculty; photographic print; Sawyer, Thomas Jefferson
    - Ballou Hall, 1875; MS036.008.023.00002.00376; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 86)
      from Munro, Tufts College - A Lecture Part 1 History, Volume 2, p. 20
    - Dean Caroline Davies, MS036.008.023.00002.00377; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 86)
      from Munro, Tufts College - A Lecture Part 1 History, Volume 2, p. 31
      People; Faculty; photographic print; Davies, Caroline S.; Jackson College
    - Dr. Fred D. Lambert, MS036.008.023.00002.00378; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 88)
      25; from Munro, Tufts College - A Lecture Part 1 History, Volume 2, p. 33
      People; Faculty; photographic print; Lambert, Fred D.
    - Dr. Alfred C. Lane, MS036.008.023.00002.00379; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 88)
      75; from Munro, Tufts College - A Lecture Part 1 History, Volume 2, p. 37
    - Inspection-Company 13 from East Hall [World War I], 1918; MS036.008.023.00002.00380; Unknown (Box Shared 86)
      from Munro, Tufts College - A Lecture Part 1 History, Volume 2, p. 38
    - Biology professor Dr. Herbert C. Neal, 1929; MS036.008.023.00002.01403; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 136)
      Dr. Herbert C. Neal; Melville S. Munro Collection, MS036/008-023#002-pg.34
      Faculty; People; photographic print; Neal, Herbert C.; Dept. of Biology
  - Tufts College: a lecture, trip, 1929 -- 1933; MS036.008.023.00003 (Box Shared 136)
  - Tufts College: a lecture, activities, 1870 -- 1930; MS036.008.023.00004 (Box Shared 136)
    - Freshman caps or "Baby Blue Bonnets", 1930; MS036.008.023.00004.00383; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 86)
      Munro Scrapbook: Tufts College - A Lecture Part 3 Activities, Vol. 4, Pg. 6 and a 2x6.5 photo contained in another Munro scrapbook, Pg. 118 or 120.
      People; Students; Traditions; Caps; photographic print
    - Football team, 1876; MS036.008.023.00004.01406; Munro, Melville S.; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 136, Box Shared 117)
      Melville S. Munro Collection - MS036/008-023#004-pg. 33 and 3x5 copy negative credited to Rollins
      Athletics; Football; People; Students; photographic print; copy negative
    - Baseball team, 1870; MS036.008.023.00004.01407; Munro, Melville S.; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 136, Box Shared 117)
      Melville S. Munro Collection - MS036/008-0023#004-pg. 37 and 3x5 copy negative credited to Rollins
      Athletics; Baseball; Students; People; photographic print; copy negative
    - Members of Tufts men's wrestling team, 1930; MS036.008.023.00004.01408; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 136)
      Melville S. Munro Collection - MS036/008-023#004-pg. 43
      Athletics; Wrestling; Students; People; photographic print
  - Tufts College: a lecture, activities, 1929 -- 1933; MS036.008.023.00005 (Box Shared 136)
  - Tufts College: a lecture, extra-curriculum, 1929; MS036.008.023.00006 (Box Shared 136)
    - Baby Party, 1929; MS036.008.023.00006.01409; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 136)
      Melville S. Munro Collection - MS036/008-023#006-pg. 107
      Events; Baby Party; Students; photographic print
  - [Tufts College and its environs], 1915 -- 1931; MS036.008.024.00001 (Box MS036 Shared 2)
  - [Tufts college and its environs], 1900; MS036.008.024.00002 (Box MS036 Shared 2)
    - The Old Powder House in Somerville, 1900; MS036.008.024.00002.01414; Unknown (Box MS036 Shared 2)
      Melville S. Munro Collection - MS036/008-024#002-pg. 3
  - [Communication], 1916 -- 1917; MS036.008.024.00003 (Box MS036 Shared 2)
  - The new gymnasium of the "Health Plant", 1931; MS036.008.024.00004; Munro, Melville S. (Box MS036 Shared 2)
- War years at Tufts, 1916 -- 1919; 1918; MS036.009; 1.25 Linear Feet
  This series contains eleven albums containing pictures about WWI. Each album is titled, "War Years at Tufts".
  - War years at Tufts, 1916 -- 1917; MS036.009.048.00001 (Box 48)
  - War years at Tufts, 1917; MS036.009.048.00002 (Box 48)
  - War years at Tufts, 1917 -- 1918; MS036.009.048.00003 (Box 48)
  - War years at Tufts, 1918; MS036.009.048.00004 (Box 48)
  - War years at Tufts, 1918; MS036.009.048.00005 (Box 48)
  - War years at Tufts, 1918; MS036.009.049.00001 (Box 49)
  - War years at Tufts, 1918; MS036.009.049.00002 (Box 49)
  - War years at Tufts, 1918; MS036.009.049.00003 (Box 49)
  - War years at Tufts, 1918; MS036.009.049.00004 (Box 49)
  - War years at Tufts, 1919; MS036.009.049.00005 (Box 49)
  - War years at Tufts, 1918 -- 1919; MS036.009.049.00006 (Box 49)
  - A Pictoral Story of the Activities of Tufts College in the World War, Vol. 1, 1916 -- 1918; MS036.009.107.00001; Munro, Melville S. (Box 107)
    folder 1 of 2
  - A Pictoral Story of the Activities of Tufts College in the World War, Vol. 1, 1916 -- 1918; MS036.009.107.00002; Munro, Melville S. (Box 107)
    folder 2 of 2
  - A Pictoral Story of the Activities of Tufts College in the World War, Vol. 2, 1916 -- 1918; MS036.009.107.00003; Munro, Melville S. (Box 107)
  - A Pictoral Story of the Activities of Tufts College in the World War, Vol. 2, 1916 -- 1918; MS036.009.107.00004; Munro, Melville S. (Box 107)
- The weather, 1908 -- 1938; 1936 -- 1938; MS036.010; 1.0 Linear Feet
  This series contains photo albums with pictures and news clippings of floods, wind, and lightning storms on campus and in nearby New England cities.
  - Pamphlets and articles regarding the weather, 1908 -- 1927; MS036.010.108.00001 (Box 108)
    Dates are approximate
  - Tufts College "After the Big Wind," Vol. 1, September, 1938; MS036.010.108.00002; Munro, Melville S. (Box 108)
    folder 1 of 3; written description by Melville S. Munro
  - Tufts College "After the Big Wind," Vol. 1, September, 1938; MS036.010.108.00003; Munro, Melville S. (Box 108)
    folder 2 of 3; photographs
  - Tufts College "After the Big Wind," Vol. 1, September, 1938; MS036.010.108.00004; Munro, Melville S. (Box 108)
    folder 3 of 3; photographs
  - Story of "the Big Wind" as told by the newspapers, Vol. 1, September, 1938; MS036.010.108.00005 (Box 108)
  - Story of "the Big Wind" as told by the newspapers, Vol. 1, September, 1938; MS036.010.108.00006 (Box 108)
  - Story of "the Big Wind" as told by the newspapers, Vol. 2, September, 1938; MS036.010.108.00007 (Box 108)
  - Story of "the Big Wind" as told by the newspapers, Vol. 2, September, 1938; MS036.010.108.00008 (Box 108)
  - Pictures of the spring floods of the year 1936, selected from the current newspapers of the time, Vol. 1, MS036.010.109.00001 (Box 109)
  - Pictures of the spring floods of the year 1936, selected from the current newspapers of the time, Vol. 2, MS036.010.109.00002 (Box 109)
  - Pictures of the spring floods of the year 1936, selected from the current newspapers of the time, Vol. 2, MS036.010.109.00003 (Box 109)
  - Pictures of the spring floods of the year 1936, selected from the current newspapers of the time, Vol. 3, MS036.010.109.00004 (Box 109)
  - Pictures of the spring floods of the year 1936, selected from the current newspapers of the time, Vol. 3, MS036.010.109.00005 (Box 109)
  - Pictures of the spring floods of the year 1936, selected from the current newspapers of the time, Vol. 4, MS036.010.109.00006 (Box 109)
  - Pictures of the spring floods of the year 1936, selected from the current newspapers of the time, Vol. 4, MS036.010.109.00007 (Box 109)
- Loose prints, 1890 -- 1959; MS036.011; 0.75 Linear Feet; 403 Digital Object(s)
  This series contains loose prints collected from various sources and attributed to Melville Munro. Loose prints are physically stored separately from the collection in accession order. See barcode in item record for location of originals.
  This series is arranged as found.
  - Jackson bicycle group, 1935; MS036.011.DO.00001; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 30, Box Shared 43)
    5 x 7, Published in the Tufts Criterion, Nov. 1980.
    Athletics; Cycling; People; Students; photographic print; copy negative; Jackson College
  - Dr. Farrington demonstrates before dental students, 1931; MS036.011.DO.00004; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 83)
    Students; Dental students; People; Faculty; School of Dental Medicine, records; Farrington, Dr.; School of Dental Medicine
  - Jackson students Judy Tarentino, Linda Haarala [?], and Dorothy Campbell, [with Jumbo], 1954; MS036.011.DO.00016; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 83)
    Date is approximate; 8 x 10
    Students; People; Phineas Taylor Barnum, papers; photographic print; Jumbo; Jackson College
  - Jackson students E. Beattie and M.D. Rourke with Jumbo, 1922; MS036.011.DO.00017; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 83)
    People; Students; Phineas Taylor Barnum, papers; photographic print; Jumbo; Beattie, E.; Rourke, M. D.; Jackson College
  - Football players with Jumbo, 1935; MS036.011.DO.00019; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 83)
    Athletics; Football; People; Students; photographic print; Jumbo
  - Melville S. Munro standing next to tripod in the snow, MS036.011.DO.00065; Unknown (Box Shared 144)
    No date; 8 x 10
    People; Faculty; photographic print; Munro, Melville S.
  - Tufts war garden, 1918; MS036.011.DO.00069; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 141)
    World War, 1914-1918; People; Students; photographic print
  - John Albert Cousens discusses College business with trustee Harold Sweet, 1930; MS036.011.DO.00075; Unknown (Box Shared 141)
    Date is approximate
    People; College presidents; photographic print; Cousens, John Albert; Sweet, Harold; Office of the President
  - Leonard Carmichael, 1920; MS036.011.DO.00091; Unknown (Box Shared 140)
    mounted 8 x 10
    Portraits; People; College presidents; Office of the President, Leonard Carmichael, records; photographic print; Carmichael, Leonard; Office of the President
  - Nathaniel Hobbs Knight, 1937; MS036.011.DO.00289; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 86)
    3.5 x 6
    People; photographic print; Knight, Nathaniel Hobbs
  - Frank W. Durkee, 1921; MS036.011.DO.00294; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 86)
    People; photographic print; Durkee, Frank W
  - Fred M. Ellis, 1938; MS036.011.DO.00297; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 86)
    5.5 x 5
    People; photographic print; Ellis, Frederick M. "Fish"; Dept. of Athletics; Faculty of Arts and Sciences
  - William J. Bennett, 1918; MS036.011.DO.00304; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 86)
    H 17.5, W 10 cm
  - Dr. Charles E. Fay, 1924; MS036.011.DO.00381; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 86)
    People; Faculty; photographic print; Fay, Charles Ernest
  - Dirrell D. Sample (1916) at desk, 1935; MS036.011.DO.00433; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 90)
    People; Alumni and alumnae; photographic print; Sample, Dirrell D.
  - The Hodgdon Gate, 1927-06-18; MS036.011.DO.00451; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 90)
    mounted on 10.5 x 8, Munro 6373
    Gates; Memorials; photographic print
  - Edwin C. Bolles, MS036.011.DO.00468; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 90)
    People; photographic print; Bolles, Edwin Courtlandt; Board of Trustees
  - Eugene B. Bowen with '76 Flag, 1936; MS036.011.DO.00469; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 90)
    5 This date is approximate.
    People; Alumni and alumnae; photographic print; Bowen, Eugene B.
  - Eugene B. Bowen with Bowen Lion in front of Barnum Hall, 1923; MS036.011.DO.00471; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 89)
  - Baseball team, 1920; MS036.011.DO.00476; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 89)
    mounted
    Athletics; Baseball; Students; photographic print
  - Tufts Varsity football squad, 1926; MS036.011.DO.00482; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 91)
    8.5 x 6
    Athletics; Football; People; Students; photographic print; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics
  - Delta Upsilon dining room, 1938-02-15; MS036.011.DO.00483; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 91)
    Housing; Food service; photographic print; Delta Upsilon
  - Delta Tau Delta house, 1936-12-16; MS036.011.DO.00484; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 91)
    Buildings; Housing; photographic print; Delta Tau Delta
  - Delta Upsilon Poverty Party, 1930; MS036.011.DO.00485; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 91)
    Student activities; photographic print; Delta Upsilon
  - Room shared by two fraternity brothers in Delta Upsilon house, 1917; MS036.011.DO.00486; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 89)
    Housing; Greek letter societies; photographic print; Delta Upsilon
  - Delta Upsilon Gang, 1936-05-11; MS036.011.DO.00489; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 91)
    Greek letter societies; photographic print; Delta Upsilon
  - Soldiers doing laundry outside of West Hall, World War I, 1916; MS036.011.DO.00493; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 89)
    mounted (UI00494 on reverse)
    World War, 1914-1918; People; photographic print
  - [Jackson College Basketball Team], 1916; MS036.011.DO.00494; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 89)
    Athletics; Basketball; photographic print; Jackson College
  - Football, 1920 -- 1925; MS036.011.DO.00504; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 89)
    25 mounted
    Athletics; Football; photographic print; Football
  - Boxing Bout, 1920; MS036.011.DO.00510; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 91)
  - Biology Club Officers, 1939-03-20; MS036.011.DO.00511; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 89)
    People; Student activities; photographic print; Biology Club
  - Zeta Psi Renovated House [80 Professors Row, formerly Shipman House], MS036.011.DO.00514; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 91)
    Buildings; Greek letter societies; Housing; photographic print; Zeta Psi
  - Dearborn Gate, 1935-06-01; MS036.011.DO.00515; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 91)
    Gates; photographic print; Dearborn, Heman A.
  - Delta Upsilon House, Hall-Interior, 1938-02-15; MS036.011.DO.00516; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 91)
    Greek letter societies; Buildings; Housing; photographic print; Delta Upsilon
  - Delta Upsilon [Fraternity] Gang, 1936-05-11; MS036.011.DO.00517; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 91)
  - Delta Upsilon Costume [Poverty] Party, B. A. Roscoe,1931, and lady, 1930-02-21; MS036.011.DO.00518; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 91)
    Greek letter societies; Student activities; photographic print; Roscoe, B.A.; Delta Upsilon
  - Miner and Paige [Halls] College Avenue, 1920; MS036.011.DO.00523; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 91)
    Buildings; photographic print; Crane Theological School; School of Religion; Divinity School
  - McCollester at his front door [48 Professors Row], 1938; MS036.011.DO.00526; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 89)
    People; Alumni and alumnae; Faculty; College administrators; Buildings; Housing; photographic print; McCollester, Lee Sullivan
  - Ivy Society, 1939-05-12; MS036.011.DO.00529; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 91)
    People; Student activities; photographic print; Hanabury, Mark; Gomez, Philip; Breen, James; Dee, John; Burch, Lorett; Gessay, Louis; Lynch, William; McMahon, William; Bachman, Everett; Ivy Society
  - Choir, 1936-03-01; MS036.011.DO.00532; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 91)
    People; Student activities; photographic print; Choir
  - East Hall Gang, 1936-05-14; MS036.011.DO.00533; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 91)
    People; Buildings; Housing; photographic print
  - East Hall Gang "Stink Weeds", 1939-05-24; MS036.011.DO.00535; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 91)
    Buildings; People; photographic print
  - Houston's house with tree down, Wind Storm, 1938-09-21; MS036.011.DO.00536; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 89)
    Buildings; Housing; photographic print; Munro, Melville S.
  - 98 Professors Row Bray House, 1921; MS036.011.DO.00542; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 89)
    Buildings; Housing; photographic print
  - Fletcher Hall [Blakeley Hall], 1926; MS036.011.DO.00548; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 89)
    post card with message from Munro to President Cousens
    Buildings; Housing; photographic print; Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy
  - Tower Cross Society, 1939-05-08; MS036.011.DO.00554; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 92)
    People; Student activities; photographic print; Pollard, David; Sherry, Ralph; Tibbs, Charles; Dineen, Joseph; Nygard, Harold; Pecheux, Henry; Hatch, Allen; Grant, Lauris; Griffin, Arthur; Bonney, E. Arthur; Tower Cross
  - Fletcher School Group 1939-1940 year, 1940-05-10; MS036.011.DO.00555; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 92)
    mounted Munro
    People; photographic print; Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy
  - The Lounge - Goddard Hall, 1939; MS036.011.DO.00556; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 92)
    Buildings; photographic print; Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy
  - Office - Goddard Hall, 1939; MS036.011.DO.00557; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 92)
  - Corner of Student's Room in Wilson House, 1939; MS036.011.DO.00558; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 92)
  - Reception Room - Wilson House, 1939; MS036.011.DO.00559; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 92)
  - View of Reading Room Edwin Ginn Librray - Goddard Hall, 1939; MS036.011.DO.00560; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 92)
  - Student Group 1938-1939 [Fletcher School], MS036.011.DO.00561; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 92)
  - Detail of Dining Room - Wilson House, 1939; MS036.011.DO.00562; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 92)
    Food service; Housing; Buildings; photographic print; Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy
  - Tufts Bowdoin Glee Club Concert (Tufts) [in Goddard Chapel] - Leo Lewis directing, 1938-02-24; MS036.011.DO.00563; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 89)
    Student activities; People; Buildings; photographic print; Lewis, Leo R.; Glee Club
  - Glee Club, 1938; MS036.011.DO.00564; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 92)
    People; Student activities; photographic print; Glee Club
  - Tufts Glee Club 1939-1940, Goddard [Chapel], MS036.011.DO.00565; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 92)
    People; Student activities; Students; photographic print; Glee Club
  - Ivy Society under Bowen Porch, 1940-05-01; MS036.011.DO.00568; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 92)
    People; Student activities; photographic print; Ivy Society
  - The Glee Club, 1930-03-19; MS036.011.DO.00569; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 92)
    mounted Munro #8819
  - Jumbo Book Staff (1935-1936), 1935-05-15; MS036.011.DO.00572; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 52)
    People; Student activities; Publications; photographic print; Murray, John; Metzer, Dorothy; Benoit, Leroy; Jumbo Book